Getting ready to head over to Haley's house to make some guacamole.
Uh oh, who's that?
Hey.
Woo.
Somebody's in the kitchen today.
what's
up you guys it's hayley and we're back with another episode of what's in my
kitchen presented by hexclad and i'm very excited because this episode is going to be
an anniversary per se and it's going to be just as chaotic and fun and
crazy as it was the first time.
So please welcome my next guest, Kendall Jenner.
I'm back.
Hey, buddy.
She's back.
Two years later.
Two?
Two.
Four.
Two years later, she's back.
She was my first guest on Who's in My Bathroom.
And Kendall has come to make her mom's famous layered dip that is
so popular amongst all of our friends, all of her family.
Yeah, I can't claim that it's the Kris Jenner way, but it's definitely my way.
So we're going to do that today, but we're also, before we do that, we
are going to make...
A passion fruit spritz.
a passion fruit spritz and the reason we're making a passion fruit spritz is because
Rode is putting out the passion fruit jelly peptide lip treatment so before we start
i think it's only right that we just have to apply
this is what we gotta do stunning stunning
It's better, right?
Well, okay, Hailey, step aside.
It's my show now.
Like.
She said no, actually we're gonna do my angle.
So that you could see.
Okay.
Yeah, so we are starting with the 818 Passionfruit Spritz.
Okay, okay, well, we're in this together.
Grab a shaker.
Oh, and the reason we're making two different ones is because mine's gonna be with
Repo.
The Hailey twist, it's fine.
The Hailey twist.
Okay, okay, we need ice though first.
Okay.
This is just to mix it up.
This is an ounce, this is a half ounce.
We're gonna do one and then this, cause it's 1.5.
Yeah.
Lots of tequila.
Really you could just go, go, go, go.
0.5 ounces of Aperol, which is right here.
So that would be the little side.
Cool.
Whoa.
why do I like that sound the Aperol sang to me I spilled a little
of my Aperol but it's okay
0.5 ounces of that's not a lot of passion fruit but
a hint maybe it's really strong guys I feel like I want to try this
passion fruit juice because
I think I'm going to do a little more Okay.
Yeah
So I feel like it's technically like one full ounce
Passionfruit Okay, so now we're squeezing limes.
Okay, but we can't waste because we need lime for later.
Okay, so we won't waste it.
Grab a knife These are our beautiful hex clad knives On our beautiful hex clad
board that they have provided with us today That was really that was a guys
I blocked her chop, but like it was a gorgeous chop so should I use
half?
Yeah let's see.
Ooh, the magnet?
Nice.
Here, give me the other half.
She's got strong hands.
No no no, Haley, come on.
I just got confused for a split second.
Are you ready for this?
Yep.
It's really, really cold.
It's really f***ing cold.
It's freezing.
Okay, but...
Oh, f***.
I forgot you're not supposed to take the whole thing off.
This is the thing.
I just made a huge mess.
Okay, we're going to pretend like that didn't happen.
We forgot.
No, we forgot the ice.
You know the ice is supposed to be in it.
This is okay.
Here you go.
I don't know what I was about to do.
I think I thought I was going to tip this over into her cup.
Definitely like a lot of ice.
Yeah.
To make it pretty.
Now, can you open that soda?
A clean kitchen is a happy kitchen, Haley.
I'm really overwhelmed right now.
Okay, okay.
Jeez, I was going to clean it up.
It's because I just...
You need to wipe...
Because we're...
I don't want passion fruit guacamole.
I'll rinse it before we continue.
Don't worry.
Nice.
I think a little more, right?
I like that sound.
The rosemary?
Yeah.
So what are you going to do?
like the whole thing or like cut it in half?
No, you just do that.
Ooh, cute.
Okay.
It's so pretty.
Where's my phone?
Wait, Hailey, get in here.
Literally stunning.
What?
So we're gonna try it now.
Cheers.
Passion fruit spritz.
I can imagine it right now, Palm Springs, by the pool, soaking up the sun.
It's like the perfect- Glowing, tan skin.
It's really fresh.
And you're out in the desert.
The added lip peptide passion fruit in the, like it's just all making so much
sense.
Yeah, it's like you put the lip on and then- And then it leaves a
little smudge and you can- And then you can smell it.
You can like lick it off.
Yeah.
I don't know that we would.
Here's a disclaimer.
Don't eat the peptide lip treatment.
Yeah, it's not edible, but it does taste fine.
So, recommendation.
Don't make your guac in the bowl that you're going to present it in.
because you want it to feel really clean.
So that's rule number one.
Oh my God, these are, I asked for perfect avocados and so far these feel
pretty freaking perfect.
Do you want me to slice two of these and you can slice two?
Yeah.
I don't ever do it like that.
Why?
So you do it like against your.
Yeah, exactly and I just like roll it around.
Yeah, that's actually probably a lot safer.
Thank you, Kendall.
Of course.
Mama can.
I'm not gonna lie, I'm kind of slaying the avocado cutting.
That's the right way.
You look so cute.
I love this little tray.
Yeah, me too.
In this hexclad board.
I've never seen that before.
It has a little tray to put all your extras, which I really am enjoying
that today.
Oh, so the origin story of this dip.
So we just called Kris Jenner to make sure we had it all right.
She started doing it in the 70s.
One of her friends used to make a dip similar, and then she kind of
put her Kris twist on it.
Kris twist.
I like that.
I think I just coined something for her.
Oh my god, she should make a drink called a Chris Twist.
Don't steal that, oh my god, you have to tell her that today.
I'll call her.
We have these scraps, we're gonna have a lot of extra stuff today and I'm
going to plop it in my little composter, which is really fun.
And very cool that you can do that.
I'm just gonna let it sit for a second because we're gonna add more stuff
after.
I like to compost because it reduces food waste.
So moving on, we got the avocados in here.
So now you're gonna mash them up.
Okay.
So can I prep anything else for you?
Can I cut anything while we wait?
I mean, you could cut open some limes.
I feel like...
Probably like two?
Two or three, yeah.
To squeeze the juice?
Yeah.
I feel like the real secret to this is this picante mild sauce.
I like the mild, I don't like spicy, so...
I would use the spicy.
Yeah, but like...
That's why I'm gonna add the jalapeno peppers.
It's fine, it's fine.
My side's gonna be my side, and your side's gonna be your side.
So since we did six, I'm gonna just like honestly eyeball it.
Yeah.
I don't throw too much.
I know my mom really does a lot.
Let's start there.
Maybe just a splash more.
Let's see where this takes us.
Okay.
And then we can always add.
Because you can't go back.
Can't go back.
You're right.
My mouth is actually watering.
Yeah.
And let me just say this to say it.
It will never compare to the Kris Jenner original, but it's pretty freaking good.
Just a splash more.
Then also these are exactly what KJ the OG would use.
This brand, the Lowry's garlic salt.
Which seasoning is that?
This one's the seasoning salt.
Seasoned salt.
There's the KJ, KJ difference.
Yeah, here's the difference.
I didn't know she did lemon.
Her mom uses lemon, she uses lime.
So that was one full one.
Let's see, this is where I start taste testing.
Okay.
The amount of lime is very important.
I was gonna say maybe just like a dash more of the Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But this is the moment, like adding the seasoning and adding the lime is like
where you really start to.
Oh, so good.
Well, you see what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Okay.
I actually think we could do a little more of a piquante too.
dash more of seasoned salt, garlic salt, picante, you know.
And then I think like maybe a half more.
Okay.
Tell me when I should get out the cheese and sour cream.
We could grab that actually, it's a good idea and you could start shredding.
The actual issue you're gonna face here is not eating all the guac before you
actually layer the dip, so.
So it's sharp cheddar, specifically sharp.
I'm just gonna do the whole block of cheese because I feel like I like
a lot of cheese.
Okay.
Now we're putting the guac into our presentation bowl.
So we want it to be clean and pretty.
So I'll scoop it in.
Definitely getting an arm workout.
That's definitely happening.
But I feel really determined because I know it's worth it.
Spread, that's probably enough.
More than enough.
Spread, spread, spread, spread, spread.
You're whispering.
Spread, spread, spread, spread.
Okay.
So this is done.
Over the last year, I feel like me and Kendall went extra deep.
They just almost caught me.
They almost caught me, little f***er.
The squeeze.
It's the squeeze because this is perfect for this.
Because usually you have to dollop it and then spread it.
Like I think, actually, I don't know.
No, I got it.
Are you sure?
Yeah, so I'm gonna start in the center and then you can still spread it,
but let's do it like this first.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, Hailey, no!
Oh, oh, oh, because of the sides.
No!
It's just, this is the baby twist.
And then you'll wipe it.
Yeah.
Okay.
You know like how they do in restaurants?
Wait, no, should I do all of it?
Are you gonna, oh, that's good.
See, that's what I get scared about.
Okay.
But that's what happens regardless.
It's just that's the hard part to make it all not come through like that.
But it's okay.
You can start with that and then put another layer.
Yeah, yeah, we'll add.
No, the squeezer is the best.
No, it's crazy.
It's a game changer.
So the sour cream is in there.
Oh, that's a good amount.
So far.
Okay, but wait.
Let's put it back on this.
This is what her mom got me for my wedding present.
Yeah.
She got me a whole set of these.
There's some bowls over here.
They're from the Ivy.
It's so beautiful.
I use them a lot.
Does she not love me as much as she loves you?
Because that's crazy.
This is my childhood and she hasn't even gotten me these.
So you should feel really special.
Now we're literally just gonna drizzle cheese.
Drizzle.
And again, the cheese and the sour cream are kind of the best part.
So throw as much on there as you feel.
Okay, good, I was hoping you were gonna say that because I'm a cheese gal.
Especially this, the sharp cheddar one.
The shredded sharp cheddar, the fresh.
Okay, I think that's good.
Now the layering is really done on, like, in my recipe.
This is where Kris Jenner would then take olives and tomatoes and whatever else she
uses.
Which I'm going to do my side.
Yeah, then she'll layer it really beautifully in this circular pattern, but we're not gonna
do that.
At least I'm not, because I love it just like this, and then I throw
like a little lime garnish on top.
I need a little spice in my life, so.
Yeah, we can add for you.
I'm gonna do fresh chopped tomato and jalapeno peppers.
All right, I'm also gonna get these jalapeno peppers out, and I'm gonna just chop
them, because they're a little bit big pieces.
Oh, smell that.
Ooh!
No.
Yeah, girl.
Why don't you like spicy stuff?
I don't know, I think it ruins everything.
It's like distracting me from all the other good that's happening in my mouth.
Or is it enhancing it?
No, not at all.
It's actually the only thing I can feel.
Cause you know it's a feeling, not a taste.
Yeah, but these are pickled, so I feel like it's a feeling and a taste.
That's, yeah, that's a different story that I don't wanna know about.
Me trying to show up the chopping like her
face.
F***ing show off.
Whatever.
Oh, your side is giving me anxiety.
Kendall.
That's the most Kendall statement I've ever heard.
We should get a pic though.
I'm going to send it to my mom.
Smile.
The Haley side, the Kendall side.
Okay, so we're about to dive into the dip, which I'm very excited about, but
something that we always do on the show is create the perfect bite.
So we need to get the perfect scoop for the perfect bite.
Are you ready?
Yeah, you're an originals girl, you don't do a scoop.
I'm just gonna do a regular chip.
I love a scoop.
I need to get a good scoop.
I think I'm gonna go back and forth and just see what feels good.
But I'll let you- I don't like this scoop.
I like how there's like a- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dip in it.
Oh, my chip broke in the bottom.
You got to be more careful, Haley.
That's a good bite, though.
This has been another episode of What's in My Kitchen presented by Hexclad with my
girl, Kendall Jenner.
Thank you for being here.
Cheers.
I hope you guys enjoyed this episode.
I hope you guys enjoy making this drink and making this insane dip that was
so good.
Don't forget to like, subscribe, and ring the notification bell, and I'll see you next
time.
Bye.
If you have, you take a sip.
And if you have not, let's clarify because last time I wasn't.
Yeah, I got a little like dicey the last time.
Lost in translation.
Never have I ever saved myself from marriage.
No, I have not.
No, you don't drink.
I have.
No, I haven't.
What?
Have you been married before and I didn't know?
No, it's not supposed to be.
have I ever?
I have not.
My mom's old house, fully haunted.
Crazy what happened.
Shower would turn on by itself, doors would slam shut, no one was around.
And then one time my dad came to me who is not like a believer
in stuff like this and was like, wait a minute, I'm actually freaked out.
I heard some in the whatever events.
Crazy, I have many stories about this house.
This is why you're so disturbed.
Sorry to you.
I quite literally just was like.